Suleyman Oner

Junior Mobile Developer

A highly determined and tenacious recent graduate of Information Technology with almost two years of experience working in various domains including finance and banking. Extensive mobile (IOS, Android & Hybrid) application development experience with strong knowledge of various programming languages including Java, Kotlin, and JavaScript. With a great passion for mobile software development, skills include analytical thinking and creative problem-solving, and wanting to be a part of a team developing cutting-edge mobile application and pursue an exemplary IT career in mobile development.



Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

github.com/suleymanoner

. +387644403683

in linkedin.com/in/suleymanoner

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Mobile Developer Finspire Technology

09/2022 - Present London, UK

Taking further the experience that I gained during the internship by creating login, accounts, transactions, deposits, transfers and payments screen for a mobile banking app. Utilizing React Native, TypeScript, MySQL to develop a mobile app for the company's primary service for data visualization. Working in an Agile methodology environment and actively attending all scrum ceremonies. Implementing GIT and GitHub for version control.

Mobile Developer - Intern Finspire Technology

09/2021 - 09/2022 London, UK

Involved in a mobile application development team working on a banking application by utilizing React Native for creating both iOS and Android applications. Working in different phases of project life cycle like design, development, and testing of application for android and iOS mobile devices. Attended in the weekly Java competition sessions within the team and always eager to learn from the other developers.

Android Developer – Intern Let's do it PL

03/2021 - 11/202

Warsaw, Poland

Worked on mobile applications by utilizing Java and Kotlin. Analyzed the requirements and designed a technical document for the requirement as a team. Worked closely with the web development team to ensure proper integration between mobile and web applications.

Software Developer – InternWell Business Promotion

06/2019 - 09/2019

Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Involved in a software development team working on designing a website by utilizing Figma design tool. Focused mainly on UI development and had hands-on experience in designing attractive landing pages. Implemented web design and development principles to build stable software.

EDUCATION

Master of Data Science

International Burch University

09/2022 - Present Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Bachelor of Information Technology

International Burch University

09/2017 - 07/2022 Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Movies (08/2023 - 09/2023) 🗗

 Mobile app was created with Flutter and Firebase that users can see latest, top-rated, upcoming movies and add them to their favorite list.

Movie Bank (07/2023 - 08/2023) 🗹

 Mobile app was created with React-Native and Firebase that users can see latest, top-rated, upcoming movies and add them to their favorite list.

Quotes (06/2022) 🗗

 Social media app was created with React-Native that users can share their favorite movie quotes.

Secure System Project (06/2022) 🗷

 Web app project was created with PHP, JS, CSS, HTML. It includes layered security challenges for website sign-up and login.

 Web app was created with PHP, JS, CSS, HTML and it allows users to save their letters and choose the date that they want to send it.

Moviesfaction (05/2021)

 Movie searching app was created with Java, and it includes latest movies that allow to users find movies, watch trailers etc.

CERTIFICATES

Cybersecurity Essentials - Cisco (03/2022 - 04/2022)

Learned how Cyber Essentials will help me protect my organisation against a range of cyber attacks.

INTERESTS

Mobile Development

Artificial Intelligence